One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Bege.
بيجي
I have no interest in assassinating Big Mom.
لستُ مهتمًّا باغتيال بيغ مام
But is she really the type of person we can kill with guns and cannons?
ولكن هل هي من النوع الذي يمكن قتله بالبنادق والمدافع؟
From what I've heard, she's like an iron balloon.
إنها برأيي بمثابة بالون فولاذي
I feel like this is going to be impossible.
أشعر بأنّ قتلها ضرب من الخيال
Yeah, if we're going to do this assassination, it has to be done in one blow.
هذا صحيح، إن كنا نعتبرها عملية اغتيال فحري بنا إنهاء الأمر بضربة واحدة وخاطفة
Otherwise, we'll be caught in a siege and get killed.
عدا ذلك سنُحاصر ونُقتل
Is an emperor really as strong as they say?
الأباطرة أقوياء للغاية كما يقال عنهم إذًا؟
Definitely! She's a monster!
بالطبع، إنها كالوحش
When we tried to retrieve Brook, she was fast asleep. But I still thought we were goners!
حتى وهي نائمة، كدنا نهلك على يدها أثناء عملية إنقاذ بروك
She killed her own son for the sake of sweets.
لقد قتلت أحد ابناءها من أجل الحلوى
On that note, why did you choose the tea party, —where all of her top officers will be in attendance—
إذًا لِمَ اخترت حفلة الشاي كمسرح للاغتيال رغم حضور أقوى أفراد طاقمها يا بيجي-سان؟
Well, I knew you guys would ask that...
سؤال وجيه
First of all, let me explain something.
:سأجيبك أولًا
Under exact conditions, we'll only need five seconds to kill Big Mom!
إن تحققت ظروف معينة، نحتاج لخمس ثواني لنتمكن من قتل بيغ مام
Only five seconds?!
خمس ثواني فقط؟
It's not only five seconds-rero !
إنها ليست مجرد خمس ثواني عادية-ريرو
It's won't be that easy to create that five second opening at the party-rero.
ليس من السهل الحصول على خمس ثواني في الحفلة-ريرو
The Big Mom Pirates comprises a bunch of skilled fighters, and they'll all be there.
يتضمن طاقم بيغ مام العديد من المحاربين الأقوياء وجميعهم سيتواجدون هناك
Within a split second, monsters like the sweet commanders will attempt to stop us-rero !
أشخاص كقادة الحلوى سيعترضون طريقنا خلال ثانية واحدة فقط-ريرو
At that point, it'll be a head-on fight, and we have no chance of winning that!
وبعدها ستنشب معارك مباشرة لا نملك فيها أدنى فرصة للفوز
This assassination plot began with the capture of Caesar.
بدأت مؤامرة الاغتيال هذه بعد أسر سيزار
My name is Gastino! Don't ever call me that in front of Big Mom!
اسمي غاستينو، إياك أن تناديني بهذا الاسم أمام بيغ مام
Listen!
اسمع
When this mission is over, you'll give me back my heart and free me!
بمجرد أن ننجز هذه المهمة، ستعيد لي قلبي وتحررني
That's what we agreed to!
هذا ما اتفقنا عليه
Don't forget that.
لذا لا تنسى
If you break your promise, I'll personally murder your son.
إن اخلفت وعدك، سأقتل ابنك بنفسي حتمًا
Don't get paranoid now, Gas-hiko! Bege will keep his word!
كفّ عن القلق حيال ذلك يا غاسهيكو إنّ بيجي رجل يفي بوعوده
Gas-hiko?! No, it's Gastino!
غاسهيكو؟ أنا غاستينو
Gas-hiko!
غاسهيكو
You little...!
أيها الوغد
Who cares what your name is? You're still a scumbag.
ومن يكترث؟ مهما كان اسمك الآن، ما زلت حثالة
Anyway, he's got a very crucial job.
...كما ترون، لديه عمل مهم وهو
That's right!
هذا صحيح
Let me show you what I made!
دعوني أريكم ما صنعته
Deadly poison gas: KX launchers!
"KX" قاذفات الغاز السام القاتلة
One will do the job, but I've got two extra, just in case!
واحدة ستفي بالغرض، لكني صنعت اثنتين إضافيتين إحتياطًا
Each of them can inject five grams of deadly organophosphate gas...
...بإمكان كل منها حقن 5 غرامات من الفوسفات العضوي السام
d-directly into your body!
فـ-في الجسد المستهدف مباشرة
It's the most audaciously sinful murder weapon in history!
إنه أخطر سلاح مميت على مر التاريخ
The gas will destroy an average human by just touching their skin.
سيدمر هذا الغاز البشري العادي بمجرد أن يلمس بشرته
So if it's injected directly into your body...
لذا إن حُقنت مباشرة في جسدك
I'm 100 percent sure...
...أنا متأكد 100%، بل 200% أنّ الشخص المستهدف
die!
سيموت
You're definitely gonna die!
حتمًا سيموت
Everyone will die!
أريد أن يموت الجميع
Okay, I get the picture.
فهمت، اتضح الأمر الآن
So you have a weapon that will kill her if it hits her?
بحوزتكم سلاح سيقتلها إن أصابها إذًا؟
No, unfortunately,
كلا، للأسف
if Big Mom is at full strength,
إن كانت بيغ مام بكامل قوتها فحتّى لو أصابتها القذيفة مباشرة، لن تخترق جلدها الصلب
There aren't that many weapons in this world that'll work against Big Mom!
نادرًا ما تجد سلاح في هذا العالم يمكنه التأثير على بيغ مام
Then it's pointless to have that thing!
كيف سيكون ذلك السلاح مفيدًا إذًا؟
You gotta look at the big picture.
ركزي فيما قلته
I said it wouldn't work when she's at full strength.
قلت بأنه لن يؤثر على بيغ مام إن كانت بكامل قوتها
There are two conditions necessary to ensure the KX launcher does the job properly!
على أكمل وجه KX ثمة شرطان ضروريان لعمل قاذفة
First we need a five-second window where no one is able to attack us.
أولًا، نحتاج موقعًا نضمن فيه عدم قدرة أحد على مهاجمتنا لمدة خمس ثواني
Secondly, Mama's body has to be weakened somehow.
ثانيًا، يجب أن نُضعف جسد ماما بطريقةٍ ما
What kind of convenient situation is that?
ما بال هذان الشرطان المفعمان بالثقة؟
What are you doing?!
ماذا تفعل؟
There is one place where all those conditions will be met...
ثمة مكان واحد سيتحقق فيه هذان الشرطان
That's the tea party!
وهو حفلة الشاي
Oh, Pez!
يا بيز
I'm sorry! Your daddy-waddy was too loud!
المعذرة، كان صوت والدك صاخبًا للغاية
It's okay, it's okay!
لا بأس لا بأس
We've been allied with Mummzie-wumzies for about a year now...
مضى أكثر من عام منذ تحالفنا مع ماما
Um, but we've never seen her get hurt.
لكننا لم نرها تتعرض للأذى أبدًا
Even when she destroyed the city...
حتى عندما دمرت المدينة
Even when bullets...
أو تعرضت لطلقات الرصاص
or bombshells hit her...
أو قذائف المدافع
Even when she sinks a ship...
وحتى عندما أغرقت إحدى السفن
We never saw her get a single scratch on her body.
لم يتعرض جسدها الصلب لأي خدش
As you said, she's just like an iron balloon.
إنها كالبالون الفولاذي كما وصفتها
But...
...لكن
there was one time I saw Mummzie-wumzie get a scratch.
ثمة مرة واحدة فقط رأيت فيها جسد ماما يتعرض للأذى
The Mother Carmel Picture Incident-rero !
أتقصد حادثة صورة الأم كارمل؟
That's right.
بالضبط
At tea parties, there's always a picture placed directly in front of Mama,
في جميع حفلات الشاي يضعون دائمًا صورة على الطاولة أمام المقعد المقابل لماما
and nobody else sits there.
ويُمنع جلوس أحد هناك
It's one of her most prized treasures.
يبدو أنّ تلك الصورة في غاية الأهمية لماما
A picture?
صورة؟
Yes.
هذا صحيح
It's a portrait of Mother Carmel!
إنها صورة للأم كارمل
You could say that it's Mama's only weak point!
يمكنكم اعتبارها نقطة ضعف ماما الوحيدة
Who is that person?
من تكون التي بالصورة؟
It seems like Mama is indebted to her, but we don't know the details.
يبدو أنّ ماما تدين لها بالكثير، لكننا لا نعرف التفاصيل
She's a figure of mystery.
إنها شخصية غامضة
Is she dead?
هل هي ميتة؟
I heard she disappeared.
سمعت أنها اختفت
So she's a missing person.
هي شخص مفقود إذًا
Even those in the family don't know the specifics.
حتى نحن أفراد العائلة لا نعرف عنها الكثير
One time at a tea party, one of the servants accidentally knocked it off of the table.
ذات مرة في إحدى حفلات الشاي أسقط أحد الخدم صورة الأم كارمل من على الطاولة بالخطأ
Mother...
...الأم
I was stunned by Mama's reaction to it.
كانت ردة فعل ماما مفاجأة من العيار الثقيل
She turned pale and let out a loud shriek that I'd never heard before!
وجهها أصبح شاحبًا، وصاحت بصرخة مدوية لم أسمع مثلها من قبل
It was different from her ravenous rampage!
الأعراض كانت مختلفة عن أعراض نوبة جوعها
All we could do was just cover our ears to protect our eardrums...
لم يكن بوسعنا سوى تغطية آذاننا لحماية طبلات آذاننا
People were passing out and collapsing one after another!
الأشخاص الذين حولها أغمي عليهم واحدًا تلو الآخر
On top of the shriek, she unleashed her conqueror's haki!
وزيادةً على تلك الصرخة، أطلقت الهاكي الملكي الخاص بها
All because of a jostled picture.
وكل ذلك فقط بسبب سقوط تلك الصورة
The point is what happened next.
والأكثر أهمية هو ما حصل بعدها
Mama knelt down from shock and, believe it or not,
في تلك اللحظة، سقطت ماما على ركبتيها جرّاء الصدمة
she scraped her knee and it was bleeding!
وجُرحت ركبتها ونزفت دمًا
I was surprised because I didn't think she had red blood flowing through her veins.
تفاجأت لأنني لم أتصور أنّ لديها دمًا طبيعيًّا أحمرًا كسائر البشر
When she breaks down like that, her body becomes fragile.
جسد ماما يصبح هشًّا عندما تصاب بحالة الانهيار تلك
So, at the tea party today, if we break that picture in half, what do you think will happen?
لذا في حفلة الشاي اليوم، إن كسرنا  تلك الصورة لنصفين ما الذي تظنونه سيحدث يا تُرى؟
Mama will be devastated!
ستُشل حركة جميع الحضور لأكثر من خمس ثواني بسبب انهيار وصرخة ماما
Then, the KX launcher will show its real strength...
بكامل قوتها KX وحينها سيأتي دور إطلاق قاذفة
and Emperor Big Mom will die!
معلنةً بذلك موت الإمبراطورة بيغ مام
The news of the assassination of Big Mom will spread across the world!
سينتشر خبر اغتيال بيغ مام في جميع أنحاء العالم
But isn't that shriek gonna paralyze us, too?
ولكن ألن تشلّ تلك الصرخة حركتنا أيضًا؟
Don't worry. We have these.
اطمئن، لدينا هذه
Invisible Symphonia System!
«نظام السيمفونيا الخفي»
Oh, earplugs!
سدادات أُذن؟
If breaking that picture creates such a big mess...
إن كان مجرد كسر تلك الصورة سيُحدث فوضى كبيرة
Then we gotta save Sanji's family during that time, too.
علينا استغلال تلك اللحظة لإنقاذ عائلة سانجي أيضًا
Hey, don't act like it'll be that easy.
أنت، لا تتوقع أنها عملية سهلة
It'll take three seconds for Mama to freak out after the picture is broken.
سيكون لدينا حوالي 3 ثواني بين كسر الصورة وبداية نوبة بيغ مام
If you're surrounded by the angry Big Mom Pirates before it gets messy,
إن حاصرك قراصنة بيغ مام الغاضبين قبل أن يصبح الوضع فوضويًّا
it'll be miraculous for you to stay alive for three seconds!
ستكون معجزة لو نجوت بحياتك في تلك الثلاث ثواني
I need you to take that role, Straw Hat!
أحتاجك في تأدية هذا الدور يا قبعة القش
Wait a minute! That means Luffy is going to be bait!
مهلًا لحظة، أتعني أنّ لوفي سيكون بمثابة الطُعم في العملية؟
Bege! Nami and her friends saved Lola!
بيجي، نامي ورفاقها أنقذوا لولا
How could you ask him to be a sacrifice?!
أنّى لك إرساله لموتٍ محتوم؟
Okay!
لا بأس
I'll do it!
سأفعلها
You need to think twice about this...
عليك إعادة التفكير في الأمر
Well, I just came up with an awesome way to arrive at the party.
على أي حال، خطرت في بالي طريقة مثيرة للظهور
A way to show up?
طريقة للظهور؟
What?! What is it? Sounds like fun! I wanna hear it!
ماذا؟ ما هي؟ تبدو ممتعة، أخبرني عنها
Me too!
أنا أيضًا
No way. If I tell you now, it'll ruin the fun.
كلا، ستكون مملة إن أخبرتكم
– What was I worried for?
ممّ كنتُ قلقة؟ -
Sounds good. Then, I'll be counting on you.
تبدو مثيرة للاهتمام، نعتمد عليك إذًا
Sure!
أجل
Now, do you know when to break the picture?
حسنًا، هل تعرف الزمن المناسب لكسر الصورة؟
When Sanji kisses Pudding, right?
أليس عندما يقبّل سانجي بودينغ؟
Idiot, I won't do that! I can't!
لن أفعل ذلك أيها الأحمق
The wedding kiss will draw everyone's attention away.
قبلة الزفاف ستجذب انتباه جميع الحضور
That's precisely when...
...في تلك اللحظة تحديدًا
Pudding-san will shoot Sanji-san !
بودينغ-سان ستطلق النار على سانجي-سان
I'll dodge her shot.
سأتفادى الطلقة، لذا سيكون إطلاق النار بمثابة الإشارة
Okay! Sounds easy!
فهمت، يبدو الأمر سهلًا
Alright, let's go over the plan.
عظيم، لنراجع الخطة
When Pudding shoots, Straw Hat will break the picture!
عندما تطلق بودينغ النار، سيقوم قبعة القش بتحطيم الصورة
Big Mom will start to shriek,
حينها سيضجّ المكان بصراخ بيغ مام
and we'll put the Invisible Symphonia System in our ears.
«ثم سنرتدي «نظام السيمفونيا الخفي
Say "earplugs."
قل سدادات أذن فقط
Then, it'll be downhill from there.
في ذلك الوقت سيحين كل شيء
While the partygoers are in a panic, you guys will rescue Germa.
بينما ينتشر الذعر بين الناس، ستنقذون جيرما
And with the KX launcher and the deadly poison gas shell,
...السامة والمميتة KX ونحن سنستخدم قاذفات
we'll assassinate Big Mom.
لاغتيال بيغ مام
This all needs to be finished in 10 seconds.
أنهوا كل شيء بغضون عشر ثواني كأقصى حد
As soon as we kill Big Mom,
حالما نقتل بيغ مام، سيحين دور هذا الأحمق
Yes, that's when I'll arrive!
أجل، سيحين دوري في الدخول
Who are you calling an "idiot"?!
من وصفته بالأحمق؟
– He's such a piece of crap. – Is this jerk part of the plan?
إنه مجرد حثالة
Shut up!
اخرسا
Listen, since I can fly, I'll plunge on to the site with a mirror to escape!
اسمعوا، بما أنني أستطيع الطيران سأقتحم المكان بمرآة للهرب برفقة هذه المرأة
I'm not part of this! Mama's gonna kill me!
لا تُقحموني في خطتكم، ستقتلني ماما
You guys did a great job bringing Brûlée here.
أبليتم حسنًا بجلب بروليه معكم
We couldn't have hoped for a more useful power to help us escape.
لم نتصور أننا سنحظى بهذه القدرة المفيدة للهرب
Your compliment doesn't make me happy, you bastard!
لن أفرح بمديحك أيها الوغد
You bastard!
أيها الوغد
Once you finish, dive into Caesar's mirror quickly!
حالما تنتهون، عليكم الدخول إلى مرآة سيزار فورًا
Big Mom will still be shrieking.
ستواصل بيغ مام هيجانها
And then, we can just run away in the mirror dimension at our own pace.
وكل ما يتبقى هو الهرب عبر بُعد المرايا
The mirror will provide you the quickest way to escape from the island.
ستوفّر لنا المرآة أسرع طريقة للهروب من هذه الجزيرة
Through the Mirro-world, we can get to the Sunny in no time.
يمكننا بلوغ السفينة سريعًا عبر عالم المرايا
That's quite a plan.
يا لها من خطة مثالية
Yeah, I think it's gonna work well!
أجل، أظنها ستنجح
These bastards...!
...هؤلاء الأوغاد
Once each of us gets to our own ships, our alliance is over.
سينتهي تحالفنا بمجرد وصول كل منّا لسفينته
We should just get out of this territory as fast as we can.
ويتبقى الهرب من هذه المنطقة بأسرع ما يمكن
Good luck in battle!
حظًّا موفقًا في المعركة
Alright!
عظيم
I guess we're set.
أظننا مستعدين
The party starts at 10:00, right?
تبدأ الحفلة في الساعة العاشرة، أليس كذلك؟
Two and a half hours to go...
تبقت ساعتان ونصف
I gotta go back to my room, since I'm the groom.
يتوجب عليّ العودة إلى غرفتي بما أنني العريس
We have to go back, too. Let's get ready for fake security duty.
نحن أيضًا علينا العودة لنستعد لتأدية حراسة مزيفة
Hey, Bege. Could you do me a favor?
أخبرني يا بيجي، أيمكنك أن تسدي إليّ معروفًا؟
What is it?
ما هو؟
When I show up in a funny way...
...حينما أظهر بطريقة مثيرة
Don't try to be funny! You're gonna die!
لا تحاول أن تكون مضحكًا وإلّا ستموت
Today is a holiday because of the tea party!
اليوم عطلة بمناسبة حفلة الشاي
Let's celebrate with Supreme cheese and beer!
لنحتفل بجبنٍ طازج وبالجعة
So, Madam Pudding's old enough to get married now.
بلغت بودينغ-ساما عمر الزواج إذًا
The groom is Germa 66's third son. We'll have a strong ally!
العريس هو الابن الثالث لجيرما 66، سنحظى بحليفٍ قوي
I heard the whole Du Feld Conglomerate has arrived.
سمعتُ أنّ عائلة دو فلد قد وصلت
A lot of prestigious guests are going to be there today.
سيحضر مجموعة من الضيوف المشاهير
Congratulations!
تهانينا
You're celebrating too early!
أنت تحتفل مبكرًا
That's okay! I'm so happy!
هذا جيّد، أنا سعيد جدًّا
Today's Prince Sanji's wedding.
اليوم حفل زفاف سانجي-ساما
The escort soldiers weren't allowed to enter the castle.
لم يُسمح حتى للحرس بدخول القلعة
Obviously, we can't attend either.
من المؤكد أننا لا نستطيع الدخول أيضًا
Of course not. No one needs a guard for a wedding.
بالطبع، لا أحد بحاجة للحراسة في زفاف
Yeah, it should be a peaceful day.
الجو هادئ اليوم
Everyone from the Vinsmoke family, good morning!
صباح الخير يا أفراد عائلة فينسموك
Yonji!
يونجي
Wake up and change!
استيقظ وبدل ثيابك
Where's Reiju? She's not in her room.
أين ريجو؟ إنها ليست في غرفتها
Oh yeah, I haven't seen her since yesterday.
على ذكر هذا، لم أرها منذ الأمس
Oh, Lady Reiju finished with her preparations in another room.
أنهت ريجو-ساما تجهيزاتها في غرفة أخرى
I see.
هكذا إذًا
There is still an hour before the tea party, so take your time.
تبقت ساعة على بدء حفلة الشاي، لذا خذوا وقتكم
W-What happened?!
مـ-ماذا حدث؟
Call the ministers!
استدعوا الوزراء
I-It's not moving! It's dead!
إ-إنه لا يتحرك، لقد مات
My cute little skeleton!
هيكلي العظمي اللطيف
That's too bad, but Mama...!
...هذا مؤسف، لكن يا ماما
Today is the tea party that you've been waiting for.
اليوم هو موعد حفلة الشاي التي كنتِ تتطلعين شوقًا لها
And what else?
وماذا أيضًا؟
♪ The wedding cake! ♪
♪ كعكة الزفاف ♪
Mr. Morgans and all the other VIPs have already arrived.
لقد وصل السيد مورغانز وجميع الشخصيات المهمة
You can't do this to me! Untie me!
أنا لن أسامحكم، حرروني-غاو
We'll leave some water and food.
سنترك لك بعض الماء والطعام
I'm sorry, but I'm sure someone'll find you soon.
أعتذر، أنا واثق أنّ أحدهم سيجدك قريبًا
Screw you!
لا تعبث معي
Where are you guys going?!
إلى أين أنتم ذاهبون-غاو؟
We're leaving this country.
سنترك هذه الدولة
What?!
ماذا؟
That's why you guys were carrying out your stuff all night long...
لهذا السبب كنتم تحزمون أغراضكم طوال الليلة الماضية
Goodbye.
إلى اللقاء
You guys are affiliates of the Big Mom Pirates, and you're leaving the country...
تتركون الدولة رغم كونكم قراصنة تابعين لبيغ مام
That means you're betraying Mama!
هذا بمثابة خيانة لماما
Does she know about this?!
هل تعرف ماما عن هذا؟
We can't let her find out.
لا يمكننا السماح لها بمعرفة هذا
She'll kill those who leave.
لأنها تقتل من يغادر
That's what she does, right?
أليست هذه طبيعة بيغ مام؟
Jinbe told us to say thanks.
جينبي يقدم امتنانه لك
Jinbe did?!
جينبي؟
We're very lucky to have heard Pekoms' story.
نحن محظوظون لسماع قصة بيكومز
I don't think Bege can pull off his plan to kill Big Mom that easily,
لا أظن أنّ بوسع بيجي تنفيذ خطته تمامًا بتلك السهولة
but I can't believe Mama is plotting to assassinate Germa, too.
لكنني أجد صعوبة في تصديق أنّ ماما تخطط لاغتيال جيرما أيضًا
If Luffy and his crew find out about it, they'll push themselves to save Sanji.
لو اكتشف لوفي ورفاقه ذلك، سيندفعون لإنقاذ سانجي
They'll be in danger, and I can't just sit back and watch! I've got to help them!
سيتعرضون لخطر محدق ولا أستطيع البقاء مكتوف اليدين، عليّ مساعدتهم
That means I will raise...
...هذا يعني أنني سأُعلن
a full-fledged rebellion!
التمرد
I will betray Big Mom.
سأخون بيغ مام
To fufill my duty to her, I tried to tell her that I was leaving.
لقد استأذنتها بمغادرة رايتها بالفعل
But I withdrew that request,
لكنني تراجعت عن ذلك
because of the numbers I saw on the roulette wheel.
بسبب أرقام الروليت
Those numbers represented the comrades who would've been victimized along with me!
كانت الأرقام تمثّل عدد رفاقي الذين سيلقون حتفهم معي
That's why I need you all to escape from here.
لهذا السبب أريدكم أن تغادروا هذا المكان جميعًا
The price that Big Mom wanted me to pay
بيغ مام كانت تود أن تُدفعني الثمن غاليًا أكثر من سلب حياتي كعقوبة
On the day of the tea party, the hors d'oeuvre ships,
«في يوم حفلة الشاي، سُفن «هور دويفور سترافق الضيوف من كل الجزر، مما سيجعل الحراسة ضعيفة
And if something happens at the tea party, it'll draw everyone's attention.
لذا إن حصل شيئًا ما في حفلة الشاي سيجذب ذلك انتباه الجميع
So that's your chance to escape!
وستحين فرصتكم بالهرب وقتها
I'm prepared for that. That won't be a problem. But Jinbe...
أنا مستعد لذلك، لا تقلق يا جينبي
All we want to do is ensure that you can be free.
نحن نود مساعدتك في الحصول على حريتك فحسب
Yes, I know.
أجل، أعرف
No, you don't!
بل لا تعرف
In order to save Straw Hat, you'd sacrifice your own life!
فأنت مستعد للمخاطرة بحياتك في سبيل إنقاذ قبعة القش
Let's say I join the Straw Hats one day...
لو أنني انضممت لطاقم قبعة القش يومًا
I will be fighting for my captain, Straw Hat Luffy, with my own life on the line!
فإني سأقاتل لأجل القبطان قبعة القش لوفي حتى لو كلفني ذلك حياتي
Aladine, it's just a matter of...
...علاء الدين، إنها مسألة
doing it now or later.
افعلُها الآن أو لاحقًا
I see. Do as you like.
فهمت، افعل ما يحلو لك
But do your best to save your own life too.
لكن ابذل جهدك لإنقاذ حياتك أيضًا
Okay?
مفهوم؟
We'll set sail for Fishman Island.
سنبحر لجزيرة البرمائيين
You're worried about the Ryugu Kingdom too, right?
أنت قلق على مملكة ريوغو أيضًا، أليس كذلك؟
Yes.
أجل
We'll protect it no matter what!
سنحميها مهما كلّف الثمن
I'm sorry!
سامحني
Don't apologize! We've known each other for decades.
توقف، نحن نعرف بعضنا منذ سنوات
We'll live to see each other again, Jinbe!
لنعش من أجل رؤية بعضنا مجددًا يا جينبي
Why would Jinbe feel the need to thank me?
لِمَ يشعر جينبي بالامتنان لي؟
Hurry up and get ready to leave!
أسرعوا وتجهزوا للرحيل
Yeah!
حاضر
Hey, wait! You bastards!
انتظروا أيها الأوغاد
Where were you, Reiju?
أين كنتِ يا ريجو؟
It's none of your business.
هذا ليس من شأنك
I know you guys were partying the whole night. So that's why I asked for a quieter room.
كنتم تحتفلون حتى وقتٍ متأخر، لذا طلبتُ تبديل غرفتي
Give a grown woman her privacy, you idiot.
لا تتدخل في أمور البالغات أيها الأحمق
Let's go. The tea party will take place on the roof.
هيا بنا، ستقام حفلة الشاي على السطح
At last, Germa 66 will have Big Mom's power on our side
وأخيرًا سنحظى نحن جيرما 66 بقوة بيغ مام إلى جانبنا
and will rule the North Blue again!
وسنحكم الأزرق الشمالي مجددًا
You're in a good mood.
أنت في مزاج جيّد
But most importantly... Hey!
...لكن الأكثر أهمية
Both the groom and the bride are fully prepared.
كِلا العريس والعروسة قد انتهيا من التجهيزات
What are you thinking, Sanji? Why didn't you escape?
ما معنى هذا يا سانجي؟ لماذا لم تهرب؟
You know what's going to happen.
أنت تعرف ما سيحدث
I'm depressed.
أشعر بالضجر
What's wrong?
ما الخطب؟
Are you nervous?
متوترة قبل الزفاف؟
I don't think so!
لا أظن ذلك
I don't want to get any blood on me after I kill that dumb Sanji.
لا أريد أن ألطخ نفسي بدماء سانجي الأحمق بعدما أقتله
And in order for everyone to continue to see me as a good girl, I'll have to erase all their memories.
وعليّ محو ذكريات الجميع كي أعود فتاة طيبة في أنظارهم
When I think about all that...
...التفكير بكل ذلك
it sounds like a pain in the ass!
لهو أمرٌ مزعج للغاية
Everyone has their own objectives...
كل طرف لديه أجندته وخططه الخاصة
and the tea party from hell will start soon!
ها قد شارفت حفلة الشاي الجحيمية على البدء
♪ It's gonna start! ♪
♪ ستبدأ ♪
♪ It's time for Mama's tea party! ♪
♪ حان موعد حفلة شاي ماما ♪
♪ It's time! ♪
♪ حان الوقت ♪
♪ A porkswagon comes a-rushing! ♪
♪ عربة الخنزير يركض عجلًا ♪
♪ I wonder if he can make it... ♪
♪ أتساءل إن كان سيصل في الوقت المناسب ♪
♪ He's late! ♪
♪ إنه متأخر ♪
♪ He has to hurry! ♪
♪ عليه أن يُسرع ♪
♪ The big guests ♪
♪ لقد وصل الضيوف الكبار ♪
♪ Why did you get invited, undertaker? ♪
♪ لماذا تمت دعوة الحانوتي؟ ♪
♪ You're so small-minded; stop it ♪
♪ يا لتفكيرك السطحي، توقف رجاءً ♪
Lady Stussy!
ستوسي-ساما
♪ Can't an undertaker celebrate people's weddings? ♪
♪ ألا يمكن للحانوتي أن يحتفل بزفاف الآخرين؟ ♪
♪ I won't have anyone who smells so much like blood talking crap about me, Du Feld! ♪
♪ لن أسمح لشخص رائحته كالدماء أن يهينني يا دو فلد ♪
♪ Hey, I'm so happy to be invited ♪
♪ مرحبًا، أنا سعيد لحصولي على الدعوة ♪
President Morgans!
مورغانز-ساما
♪ This marriage will be big news! Germa and our company are strongly tied ♪
♪ هذا الزواج سيكون خبرًا مهمًا، فجيرما وشركتنا على علاقة قوية ♪
♪ But it's a story that has already been spread across the underworld ♪
♪ لكنه خبر منتشر في العالم السفلي بالفعل ♪
♪ So it's too old! ♪
♪ إنه قديم للغاية ♪
♪ That's right, that's right ♪
♪ ذلك صحيح ♪
♪ It doesn't need to be transported ♪
♪ لا حاجة لإعادة سرده ♪
♪ Hi there, how are you? Welcome! ♪
♪ حللتم أهلًا ووطئتم سهلًا، تفضلوا ♪
Perospero-kun !
بيروسبيرو-كن
♪ Kingpins of the underworld, ♪
♪ يا قادة العالم السفلي ♪
♪ Would you like me to... Lick... ♪
♪ لذا أتسمحون لي بأخذكم إلى هناك؟ ♪
♪ By the candy escalator! ♪
♪ إنه سُلّم الحلوى المتحرك ♪
– This is amazing! – His candy sculptures are always...
هذا مبهر
♪ ...a true work of art! ♪
♪ فنية للغاية ♪
I'm humbled.
أخجلتم تواضعي
Mama hates late arrivals.
ماما تبغض المتأخرين
So, shall we?
لذا هلّا ذهبنا الآن؟
Oh, the staircase is moving!
هذا السُلّم يتحرك من تلقاء نفسه
How beautiful!
يا لجمالة
This is great. Very easy.
هذا جيّد، إنه مريح وسهل
See you later.
رافقتكم السلامة
You can have these.
خذوا، يمكنكم تناول هذه
Wait three minutes and you can lick the candy escalator.
انتظروا ثلاث دقائق وبعدها يمكنكم لعق حلوى السُلّم أيضًا
Now, I've gotta go, too.
والآن، عليّ الذهاب أيضًا
It smells good.
يا لها من رائحة زكية
Please come in.
رجاءً تفضلوا بالدخول
This place always looks so delicious.
يبدو هذا المكان شهيًّا كعادته
Welcome, guests.
أهلًا بكم أيها الضيوف
Hi, Smoothie.
مرحبًا يا سموذي
Would you like a welcoming drink?
أتودون شرابًا ترحيبيًّا؟
Today, we have a little bit of Mount Mauri lava, a beautiful woman who stabbed a thousand men,
لدينا اليوم جزء من حمم ماوري البركانية
and a giraffe that makes funny sounds.
وزرافة تصدر صراخًا مضحكًا
– l'll have a cup of the giraffe. – Me too.
أريد كوبًا واحدًا من الزرافة
Okay. I'll squeeze it now.
حسنًا، سأعصر لكما حالًا
That's hilarious!
هذا مضحك فعلًا
Here you go.
تفضلا
It tastes so good. And it's smooth to drink, too.
مذاقه سلس ورائع
Open up!
افتحوا
I refuse to be searched!
أرفض تفتيشكم الجسدي
No, you can't do that, Mr. Jigra.
هذا غير مسموح أيها السيد جيغرا
Let go of me!
أفلتوني
I said let go of me!
أخبرتكم أن تفلتوني
Is Big Mom already inside?
هل بيغ مام في الداخل؟
See, I had an invitation from the last tea party.
لقد حصلتُ على دعوة لحفلة الشاي السابقة
But sadly, I was unable to be here.
لكنني لم أتمكن من الحضور
I had to attend my mother's funeral!
بسبب جنازة والدتي
I wrote my reasons in a letter,
كتبتُ رسالة أوضح فيها ذلك
but guess what Big Mom sent me in response!
لكن ماذا كان رد بيغ مام برأيكم؟
It was my hospitalized father's...
...كان رأس والدي الراقد
Hey! Who shot?! He's a guest!
أنتم، من أطلق النار؟ لقد كان ضيفًا
You are...
...أنت
Sweet Commander Katakuri!
قائد الحلوى كاتاكوري
Why did you shoot him?!
لِمَ أطلقت عليه؟
This is what he was going to say:
:هذا ما كان سيقوله
"...but guess what Big Mom sent me in response!"
«ماذا كان رد بيغ مام برأيكم؟»
"It was my hospitalized father's head."
«كان رأس والدي الراقد في المشفى»
"I'm here today to get revenge."
«لقد جئتُ للانتقام»
"Open the gate."
«افتحوا البوابة»
Bang.
نار
Bang, he shot.
يطلق النار
Two of your men would've been shot.
ويسقط شخصان من رجالك
Is it wrong for me to throw a jelly bean at him before that could happen?
...هل من الخاطئ إصابته بحبة الهُلام وأمنع حصول ذلك
Rook Bege.
يا قطعة القلعة بيجي؟
Tell Mama that I made the decision.
أخبر ماما أنني من اتخذ القرار
This is what you're gonna say now:
:هذا ما ستقوله الآن
"I see."
«فهمت»
"Alright then."
«لا بأس إذًا»
He'll be the biggest pain in the ass at the party.
إنه أكثر شخص مزعج في هذه الحفلة
His observation haki is so good that he's able to see slightly ahead into the future.
لقد صقل هاكي الملاحظة الخاص به حتى أصبح بإمكانه رؤية لمحات من المستقبل القريب
His bounty is over a billion.
لا عجب بأنّ مكافأته تخطت المليار
He's a monster!
إنه وحش
I see. Alright then.
فهمت، لا بأس إذًا
It's about time.
حان الوقت
It's time for the tea party.
حان موعد حفلة الشاي
Everyone! Thank you for coming all this way!
شكرًا لكم جميعًا على قدومكم
Wherever you look, all you see are sweets!
أينما نظرتم ستجدون الحلوى في كل مكان يحيط بكم
Eat!
كلوا
Drink!
اشربوا
And enjoy the party to your heart's content!
واستمتعوا من أعماق قلبكم
Enjoy everything...
استمتعوا
that'll take place here!
بكل ما سيحدث هنا
Cheese Town, Milk Island
جزيرة الحليب - بلدة الجبن
Peanuts Town, Nuts Island
جزيرة المكسرات - بلدة الفول السوداني
Chocolat Town, Cacao Island
جزيرة الكاكاو - بلدة الشوكولاتة
Kingdom of Germa
مملكة جيرما
Whole Cake Chateau
قصر الكعكة الكاملة
Guestroom on the Midbaum 6th Floor
غرفة الضيوف - الدور السادس - باوم
Big Mom's Bedroom, 9th Floor
غرفة نوم بيغ مام - الدور التاسع
Eastern Inlet, Whole Cake Island
المدخل الشرقي لجزيرة الكعكة الكاملة
Aladine First Mate of the Sun Pirates
أول عضو لقراصنة الشمس علاء الدين
Charlotte Praline, Aladine's Wife 21st Daughter of the Charlotte Family
الابنة 21 لعائلة شارلوت - زوجة علاء الدين شارلوت برالين
Whole Cake Chateau
قصر الكعكة الكاملة
Pudding's Room
غرفة بودينغ
Loan Shark King
ملك الاحتيال
Queen of the Pleasure District
ملكة منطقة المتعة
Major Undertaker
الحانوتي العظيم
President, World Economy Newspaper
رئيس صحيفة الاقتصاد العالمية
Warehouse Kingpin
قائد مستودع نقابة الجريمة
Shipping King
ملك الشحن
Outside the Tea Party
أمام مدخل حفلة الشاي
Organ Dealer Jigra
تاجر أعضاء جيغرا
One of the Three Sweet Commanders
أحد قادة الحلوى الثلاث
Big Mom Pirates
قراصنة بيغ مام
Second Son of the Charlotte Family
الابن الثاني لعائلة شارلوت
"God of Fortune"
«إله الثروة»
Du Feld
دو فلد
Stussy
ستوسي
Drug Peclo
درغ بيكلو
"Big News"
«الأنباء الصادمة»
Morgans
مورغانز
Giberson
«المُخفي»
"The Concealer"
غيبرسون
"Deep-Sea Currents"
«تيار المحيط العميق»
Umit
أوميت
Bounty: 1,057,000,000 Belly
المكافأة: مليار و57 مليون بيري
Charlotte
شارلوت كاتاكوري